flipter.com 2012-03-01

# Flipter

## Flipter Privacy Policy

We value your privacy and take it seriously. This Privacy Policy describes Flipter's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when using our website or 3rd party applications.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@flipter.me

**Information Collection and Use**

**Information Collected Upon Registration:** When you create or update a Flipter account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, username, password, email address, country, age and gender.

Some Services, such as search, public user profiles and viewing and browsing through out Flipter content do not require registration.

Some of this information, for example, your name and username, is listed publicly on our Services, including on your profile page and in search results. Other personal information such as Birthday, Gender, country and your email address are not listed publicly.

**Voting on Flipter:** When you cast your opinion on Flipter data of your preferences and opinions is stored, and the information above listed is used to create statistics and demographics as a part of the collaborative flow of information on Flipter. Your name and opinion might be shared with the creators of the questions, your vote preferences will be stored and listed on the statistics page of each content item, but you can turn off these settings by managing your profile page privacy settings. And see and change who can view your opinion.

**Additional Information:** You may provide us with additional information to make public, such as a short biography, your location, or a picture. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or to market to you. You may unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained within the messages or the instructions on our web site. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request.

**User Generated Content:** If you create content or questions on Flipter this will be publicly available unless otherwise stated by you at the moment of your posting.

**  
Links to Other Web Sites:** We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies.

**Modifying Your Personal Information:** If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.

**Our Policy Towards Children:** Our Services are not directed to people under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. Should you required our action on removing an account that does not match this policy please contact us at privacy@flipter.com

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy:** If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this page to keep you informed of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.  
If you have any questions about our practices or this privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@flipter.me
